TITLE: THIS LIFE I LIVE
This life I live is not my own
For my Redeemer paid the price
He took it to be His alone
To be His treasure and His prize
The things of earth I leave behind
To live in worship of my King
His is the right to rule my life
Mine is the joy to live for Him
I died to sin upon the cross
I'm bound to Jesus in His death
The old is gone and now I must
Rely on Him for ev'ry breath
With ev'ry footstep that I tread
What mysteries He has in store
I cannot know what lies ahead
But know that He has gone before
There is a voice that pierced the grave
A power that rolled the stone away
A sound of life I know I'm saved
The voice of God has called my name
So I will rise and in the air
Behold the glory of the King
I will not fear to meet Him there
I know my life is hid with Him